Zhao SongXun

I am a full-stack developer with 7 years of experience.

Hired by many clients and several startups including Producement, Live Bela LLC ,and Tranzport, I worked on several fintech projects and improved KPIs of existing projects.

I prefer working in an agile, fast-paced working environment remotely. because I believe autonomous, self-motivated and fast-paced working is critical for a developer's career.

With solid knowledge and experience in PHP, Node.js, Python, HTML, CSS, Javascript, I always strive to produce a fully tested and efficient code based on perfect OOP design and strict coding style.

Now, I am interested in CI/CD using Github & Gitlab pipeline to various cloud patlforms.

I can provide:

- Full-time work for 5 days per week
- Suggest new ideas and apply the latest technologies
- Real-time communication
- Lead development

EMPLOYMENT

2020 - Present

FULL STACK DEVELOPER - Producement

- + Partnered with Pactum
 - * Developed Pactum chatbot
 - * Main tech stack: Java, Spring framework, React, Redux
 - * Worked as a full-stack developer, accepted by Walmart, raised 2 million USD
 - * Configuring opentelemetry and spring metrics
- + Partnered with PayQin
 - * Developed Paypal like payment mobile application
 - * Main tech stack: Flutter framework.
 - * Worked as a full-stack developer, released PayQin mobile application.
 - * Solved GCP proxy problem
- + Partnered with Salv
 - * Developed financial crime detection website

(86) 15998333742| songxunzhao1991@gmail.com

- * Main tech stack: Java, Spring framework, React
- * Worked as a full-stack developer
- + Clean Kitchen
 - * Improved shopify website for better conversion flow
 - * Main tech stack: Shopify, React, Redux, Java, Spring
 - * Worked as a full-stack developer

Tech stacks: Spring Boot, Java, Kotlin, Spock framework, React, Javascript, Flutter

Website address: www.producement.com

2018 - 2018

FULL STACK DEVELOPER - Entybox

- + Fixed bugs and improved performance of legacy website
- + Implement new design and features using Django + Angular stack

Tech stacks: Python, Django, Angular, HTML5 Video, Video streaming **Website address:** www.entvbox.com

2017 - 2018

FULL STACK DEVELOPER- Live Bela LLC

- + Launched Belacam photo sharing website using Python + Angular Stack
- + Delivered performance-driven and user-friendly website with better UI/ UX design

Tech stacks: Python, Django, Angular, Cryptocurrency, AWS Lambda **Website Address:** www.belacam.com

2017 - 2017

NETWORK SECURITY ENGINEER - Moonrock Consulting

- + Utilized VSphere to run automation scripts
- + Launched firewall management website

2016 - 2017

BACKEND DEVELOPER - Tranzport LLC

- + Developed API using Python + Django RESTful framework
- + Delivered mobile application backed by API service

2016 - 2016

FRONTEND DEVELOPER - Play TAGG Limited

- + Developed new features and fixed UI/UX bugs
- + Implement new design

2015 - 2016

FRONTEND DEVELOPER - Spoilt Social TV

+ Developed new features and fixed UI/UX bugs

EDUCATION

- + Studied computer science, speech recognition, digital signal processing
- + Submitted thesis for Noise reduction in speech

SKILLS

- Various languages and frameworks for web backend development.
- .NET/C#, Python/Django & Flask, NodeJS/Koa, Loopback, MEAN, MERN stack, Mongoose, PHP/Laravel, Symphony,
- HTML, HTML5, CSS and various CSS architectures including SMACSS, BEM, OOCSS.
- Frontend MVC, MVVM, Component based frameworks
- Angular(any version), ReactJS, Nuxt, Vue.js, Next, Webpack, Babel, Javascript ES6
- Project Analysis
- Project Scheduling
- Test Automation
- Infrastructure Design

ACHIEVEMENTS

SMOCKSY T-SHIRT WEBSITE

https://smocksy.com

BELACAM PHOTO SHARING WEBSITE

https://belacam.com

TOPTENPERCENT COMPANY WEBSITE

https://toptenpercent.com

JEWELRY SHOPPING WEBSITE

https://thefutureofjewelry.com

CUBAN CIGARS WEBSITE

https://finestcubancigars.com

PACTUM CHATBOT

https://pactum.com

TULEVA PENSION WEBSITE

https://www.tuleva.ee/en/

EXTERNAL LINKS

(86) 15998333742| songxunzhao1991@gmail.com

inkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/zhao-songxun-73a990203/

Github https://github.com/songxunzhao

Stackoverflow https://stackoverflow.com/users/6879870/songxunzhao